大眼睛 我是眼镜蛇06/刚进入通往0.4号通道的领地
Big eye, this is cobra 06, just entering the country**
请求一份标记好指向目标的/多数路径组合图
approaching way point acquring combinaton ** post approach
收到眼镜蛇06 大眼睛在等待批准
Roger cobra 06, big eye waiting for confirmation
再多等一会儿的话 大眼睛
We wait any longer,big eye,
我们就很被动了/我在这儿无法精确急转弯
we're not gonna have any choice in the/matter. I can't exactly do a u-turn here.
收到 眼镜蛇 等待批准
Roger that,cobra. Hold for confirmation.
cooper上校 你还好吧?
Captain cooper,are you okay?
发生什么了? 你刚才没有回应
What happened? You weren't answering.
因为该死的通讯同步中断了
Because the damn/comcord got disconnected.
你们花了10亿美金在航空控制系统上
You spend a billion/dollars on the avionics
却懒得检查一下通讯连接?
and don't bother to/check the comm connection?
你飞行前我检查了两遍--
No,I checked that twice/before you got in--
下次你要我们试飞新模型
and the next time you/ask us to test a prototype,
最好方向罗盘别乱转
it'd be nice if your directional/gyro didn't spin like a top
- 我可是在500英尺的空中/- 抱歉
- when I'm supposed to be 500 feet off the floor./- I'm sorry.
我会检查模拟设备 看能不能找出问题在哪
I'll go review the simulation,see/if I can figure out what went wrong.
这男人是谁?
Who is this man?
来吧 猜猜
Come on,take a shot.
不是每次给错答案 我都会炒掉你们
I'm not gonna fire you every/time you get a wrong answer.
张伯伦/(二战时英国首相)
Neville chamberlain.
你出局了
You're fired.
这男人的样子/像是会把捷克割让给法西斯的人吗?
Does this man look like he's ceding/czechoslovakia to a fascist dictatorship?
这是Buddy Ebsen 演员
It's buddy ebsen,the actor.
他已经过世了
He's dead.
- 为什么-/- Buddy本来该演绿野仙踪里的铁皮人
- Why are we- - buddy ebsen was the/original tin man in the wizard of oz.
可才一天
For a day.
他被诊断对妆容中的铝尘过敏
He was diagnosed allergic to/the aluminum dust in the makeup.
肺衰竭 他差点死掉
His lungs failed,nearly died.
问题时 为什么?
Question is,why?
你不是刚说过他过敏么?
Didn't you just say he was allergic?
也许你的双腿不健全 但耳朵都在
You may not have legs,but you got ears.
建议你使用它们 我说他被诊断为过敏
I suggest you use them. I/said he was diagnosed allergic.
既然现在缺少一个真正有趣的病例
Since we are currently short/exactly one interesting patient,
就来弄明白在1938年/Buddy Ebsen身上究竟发生了什么
we are gonna figure out what really/happened to buddy ebsen in 1938.
一方面 他是死不了第二回
Now,on the one hand,he's/not getting deader.
另一方面 你们的工作却命悬一线
On the other hand,your/jobs hang in the balance.
- 所以-/- House
- So-/- house.
我回来时 要七个可供选择的诊断
I want seven alternate/diagnoses when I get back.
你忘记怎么数到三了?
Did you forget how to count to three?
我的预算是三个
I get budget for three.
不意味着我只能雇三个
Doesn't mean I can only hire three.
事实上 恰恰就是这个意思
Actually,that's exactly what it means.
过去三年里 我压低固定薪水10%
I cut the permanent salaries by 10%.
临时对付27个人的缺口就绰绰有余
Over three years,that'll more than/make up for the breakage on the 27
下面几周我就要筛选他们
that I'm gonna weed out/over the next few weeks.
这儿有40个人
There's 40 people in there.
D排 你们出局了
Row d,you're fired.
我没有仔细数过简历
I didn't actually count all the resumes.
这很愚蠢
This is stupid.
你管不了这么多人
You can't manage that many people.
你不过是任意筛选他们
You're just gonna keep/weeding them out arbitrarily.
难道让他们坐在我的办公室里闲扯
Sure,and having them sitting/in my office schmoozing about
最喜欢哪部阿尔及利亚冲浪电影/会更有利挑选么?
their favorite algerian surfing/movies is a much better system.
- 等一下 你是D排的?/- 是的
- Wait a sec,were you in row d?/- Yes.
抱歉 我的老板说我武断又愚蠢
My apologies,my boss says I'm/being arbitrary and stupid.
D排留下 C排出局
Row d is not fired. Row c is fired.
好极了 谢谢
Great. Thank you.
看 这可不是任意的
See,that was not arbitrary.
我想多聊会 可我被呼叫了
Well,I'd love to/chat,but I've been paged.
有意思
That's interesting.
竟然是被自己呼叫
Apparently paged myself.
如果你拿的是简历 我没兴趣
If you have a resume/there,not interested.
但我很愿意听听你怎么弄到我呼机号的
But I wouldn't mind hearing/how you got my pager number.
不是简历
It's not a resume.
50,000美金
$50,000.
是独眼Nicky让我拿去给大鼻子Jimmy?
Does one-eyed nicky want me/to run that to jimmy the nose?
这是付医疗费的
It's for my medical bills.
我需要你查出我有什么病
I need you to find out/what's wrong with me.
医疗保险通常比这便宜
Well,insurance is/usually cheaper than that.
现金意味着你想隐藏
Cash means there is something to hide.
我是一名即将接受新任务的空军上校
I'm a captain in the air force/about to start a new assignment.
NASA (美国航空与航天管理局)/的航天员培训计划
Nasa's astronaut training program.
我发现了盐 创造了调频电波
I discovered salt and created fm radio.
我的眼睛和耳朵 出了问题
Something is wrong./With my eyes,my ears.
如果可以治疗 空军会承担医药费
Well,if it's fixable,the air/force will do it for free.
如果不能治 也没什么关系
If not,doesn't matter.
有100个申请者等着取代我的位置/他们可不需要治疗
There are 100 applicants ready to take/my place who don't need to be fixed.
我不能让治疗留在病历上/我做了调查
I need to do this off the/books. I did the research.
你是最棒的 无视规则 除了自己谁也不关心
You're the best,you break rules,and you/don't care about anyone except yourself.
好吧 就算是真的
Well,let's say that's true.
你得到新工作 医院得到一大笔现金
You get a new job,hospital/gets a nice wad of cash.
我得到什么?
What do I get?
我撞坏了一个模拟飞行器
I crashed a flight simulator
因为我的眼睛开始听见
because I started to hear with my eyes.
- 铝可能污染了-/- 我不关心
- The aluminum could've/been tainted- - don't care.
新病人
New patient.
30岁女性 共感觉
30-year-old female/with synesthesia.
新规则
New rules.
你们写下的实验报告 粉碎它
You generate a lab report,you shred it.
X射线报告 熔化掉
X- ray,you melt it.
没有笔记 记录 什么都不留
No notes,no records,nothing.
就你们而言 这病人是奥萨马·本·拉登
As far as you're concerned,the/patient is osama bin laden.
这房间外的人都是三角洲特种部队
And everyone not in/this room is delta force.
有问题吗?
Any questions?
我们在保护奥萨马·本·拉登?
We're protecting osama bin laden?
这只是个比喻 习惯一下
It's a metaphor. Get used to it.
还有别的问题吗?
Any more questions?
你不打算告诉我们 她的名字?
And you're not even/gonna tell us her name?
你觉得名字和她生什么病有关?
You think her name might be/connected to what's wrong with her?
奥萨马来了!
Here's osama!
现在你们都有编号 按字母顺序来
Now,you all have numbers,so we're/gonna do this alphabetically.
8 15和5
8,15,and 5.
共感觉是新症状吗?
Is the synesthesia new?
是的
Yes.
- 曾有过相似症状或精神疾病/- 不 没有
- Any history of similar symptoms/or psychiatric- - no,nothing.
你在服用处方药吗?
Are you on any prescription meds?
- 或者其他什么药物?/- 没有
- Or use any other drugs?/- No.
能信任她的回答吗?
Should we trust her answers?
你觉得我会找个吸毒者换下Buddy Ebsen?
You think I'd pull you off/Buddy Ebsen just for a junkie?
我们能信任你的答案吗?
Can we trust your answers?
- 你总要相信某人 对吧?/- 不
- Well,you gotta trust someone,right?/- No.
你周围的人最近有生病吗 家人 同事?
Has anyone close to you been sick/lately,a family member,a coworker?
不 至少我没注意到
No,not that I'm aware of.
两个倒下了 Kitty carlisle上/(女演员 出演电视辩论秀 )
Two down. Kitty carlisle.
你常常在20,000英尺高空飞行?
You spend much time above 20,000 feet?
为什么问这个?
Why would you ask that?
总是飞行的人长时间不动
People who fly are/immobile for long periods.
可能是腿部的凝块因心脏卵圆孔未闭/栓塞大脑
Could be a leg clot that embolized/to the brain through a pfo.
不寻常的见解
Unusual choice.
就像你说的 不会因为寻常的事/打断buddy的病例
Well,like you said,you wouldn't/interrupt buddy with anything that wasn't.
病人确实
The patient is.
经常飞行
A frequent flier.
13 32 39
13,32,39.
给Osama做脑电图 核磁共振 血管造影
Get Osama an eeg,mri,and angiogram.
你们中有谁认为Oswald是单独行动的?/(刺杀肯尼迪的凶手)
How many of you think/that oswald acted alone?
如果你指的独自是他没发现中情局--
If,by alone,you mean that/he was unaware that the cia--
哦 闭嘴
oh,shut up.
你一人分饰二角
Split yourself into two groups.
检测她的血液和粪便
Test her blood. Test her stool.
谁喜欢棒球指定打击?
Who likes the designated hitter?
你们错了 很幸运你们没有出局
You're wrong. You're/lucky you're not fired.
分为两组 脂多糖检测和细菌培养
Two more groups. Lps and cultures.
谁不知道指定打击是什么意思
Who doesn't know what/a designated hitter is
好的 这是她家地址
okay,here's her address.
你们闯去她家 找出她隐瞒了什么
I want you to break in,find/out what she's hiding.
为什么不能直接问病人要钥匙?
Why don't we just ask/the patient for the key?
如果能问出隐瞒什么/恐怕就要重新定义"隐瞒"了
Well,if you could find out what she's hiding/just by asking,we'd have to redefine "hiding.
你要住在这国家 得学习这里的语言
you wanna live in this/country,learn the language.
我们剩下的人做什么?
What do you want the rest of us to do?
30个人竞争上岗 你们就洗洗我的车吧
30 people for three openings,and I/want you to wash my car.
这不是我在医学院苦学的原因
This is not why I busted/my ass in med school.
我们花半个钟头洗车 没什么大不了
We spend half an hour/cleaning a car,big deal.
这是贬低身份
It's demeaning.
劳作低下?
Work is demeaning?
我们大才小用?
We're too/good for this--
别跟我说什么/辛苦劳动是恩赐
oh,don't give me that/honest day's labor crap.
我们上医学院是为了不用辛苦地劳作
We all went to med school so we wouldn't/have to do an honest day's labor.
只不过是劳动一小时
What about an honest hour's labor?
作为交换 我们得到/跟世上最好的诊断学家学习的机会
In exchange,we get a shot at learning from/one of the best diagnosticians in the world.
不 没机会了
No. We don't.
如果有机会 我们会去抽血和检查毒素
If we did,we'd be one of the ones/drawing blood or checking for toxins.
我们完了
We're done.
他不放我们走 是还要利用我们/掸尘 浆衬衫
He's just not gonna cut us loose until we've/dusted his shelves and starched his shirt.
我不干了 谁和我一起?
I'm outta here. Who's with me?
他不是开玩笑吗?
Are we sure he wasn't joking?
也许这是一个测试
Maybe this is just a test.
一切都是玩笑 都是测试
Everything's a joke,and/everything's a test.
他要我们做 来吧 快上来
And he wants us to do/it. Come on,get up here.
我本来可以试试/但我在1987年拉伤了肌肉
I could try,but I pulled a muscle in 1987
我浪费两年重读医学院/可不想被逮捕驱逐出境
I didn't waste two years repeating/medical school to be arrested and deported.
为什么要重读?
Why'd they make you repeat?
难道是体育学分不够?
Not enough gym credits?
根据新泽西州的法律
According to the state of new jersey,
我国家的医学院 在这个国家不被承认
medical schools in my country suffer/from not being from this country.
如果你弄开窗户 你得下来帮我进去
You know,if you get it open,you're/gonna have to come down and let me in.
或者你可以等在外面
Or you could just wait out here.
这是个竞争
This is a competition.
改变主意了?
Change your mind?
没有
No.
- 那你为什么回来?/- 从没打算放弃
- Then why are you here?/- Never intended to quit.
- 那刚才你为什么-/- 打算让其他人放弃
- Well,then why did you- - intended/to get everyone else to quit.
别擦了
Get off the car.
我得洗车
I need to clean it.
我们得洗车
We need to clean it.
我偷到他的车钥匙 我们开去洗车处
I stole his keys. We'll/take it to a car wash.
他让人闯进女病人家里
He's got people breaking/into a woman's apartment.
显然 这里的规则不包括尊重个人财产
Obviously,respecting personal/property isn't one of the rules.
我告诉看门人 很担心我侄女
I told the super I was/worried about my niece.
她一直不接电话
She hasn't been answering the telephone.
他是个好人/有两个女儿 住在蒙特荷约科
Nice guy. Two daughters/at mount holyoke.
没有血块
No evidence of clots.
除了血红细胞上升
And other than elevated red blood/cell counts,uh,the,uh,blood work was.
血液检查没什么特别的
Unremarkable.
你看到裸女图会不舒服?
Got a problem with/the naked female form?
一点也不
Not at all.
也许她不习惯的是裸体海豚
Maybe she's just not used/with the naked dolphin form.
那不是海豚 是一只鼠海豚
That's not a dolphin. It's a porpoise.
这是有区别的
There is a difference,you know.
至少 要求的报酬就有区别
Salary,for one thing.
我们过会儿再来?
You want us to give you a minute?
- 高红细胞数可能意味着--/- 一氧化碳中毒
- High red blood cell count likely/means-- - carbon monoxide poisoning.
针对升高的红细胞数有许多不同解释
There are a lot of different/explanations for elevated red blood cells.
没错 哪一个最吻合/鉴于你们的竞争对手
Yeah,well,which one fits best/with the damaged fluid that
在Osama的洞里发现煤气壁炉泄漏
your competitors found in the/gas fireplace in Osama's cave?
车洗干净了
Car's clean.
你看见一个口音做作的金发男人么?
Did you just see a blond guy/with a pretentious accent?
- 口音是看不见的/- 有道理
- Can't see an accent./- Good point.
车钥匙可以还给我吗?
Can I have my car keys back?
车钥匙还我 送病人去高压氧舱
Gimme the car keys,put the/patient in a hyperbaric chamber,
再也不给你那么好的质数号码了
and no more prime numbers for you.
谢了
Thank you.
这些高压氧气能够冲刷走你体内的一氧化碳
The high pressure and oxygen will flush/the carbon monoxide from your system.
大量的氧气停留时间过长是有毒害的/所以分成几次进行
This much oxygen for too long can have some/toxic effects,so we'll do this in cycles.
能跟你谈谈吗?
Can I talk to you a second?
你一直在摆弄那东西 没问题吧?
You're working that thing all/the time. Is everything alright?
我们本应该好好观测她的心率和血压
We're supposed to be watching/her heart rate and blood pressure.
我在看啊 直到你把我拖过来
Yeah,I was until you/pulled me over here.
- 我发咨询建议给另一个病人/- 好吧
- I'm sending out a consult on another patient./- Okay.
怎么了 在确认找到新工作前/我是不会辞去工作的
What? I'm not quitting my old job/until I'm sure I've got a new one.
- 我什么也没说/- 你的表情别扭
- didn't say anything./- You had a look.
也许 抱歉
Yeah. I did.Sorry.
她大概是心脏病发了
I think she's having a heart attack.
没 我只是感觉怪怪的
No,I just feel a little funny.
心律失常
Tachyarrhythmia.
心脏停跳
Ca
没反应
nothing.
室颤
V/- fib.
- 搞什么/- 离手
- Hey,where the/hell is- - clear.
你疯了吗? 不能用这个
Are you crazy? You can't bring those.
- 我们在高压氧舱里.../- 离手
- We're in/a- - clear.
她着火了!
She's on fire!
她的心脏跳动了
Her heart's beating.
我们被炒定了
And we are so fired.
我们给她用了硝化甘油和血液稀释剂
we've started her on/nitro and blood thinners.
电解质和停跳后的心电图正常
Electrolytes and/post-arrest ekg were normal.
发作不是由治疗引发的
The attack was not/caused by the procedure.
那到底是什么造成了共感觉/高红血球细胞和心脏病发?
So what does cause synesthesia,high/red blood cell count,and heart attack?
难道不用讨论是什么造成了/皮肉烧伤吗?
Aren't we gonna discuss what caused/the sudden appearance of burnt flesh?
他把电击设备弄到充满氧气的屋子里
He brought charged paddles/into an oxygenated room.
你也没阻止他
And you didn't stop him.
要么是你那时也觉得可以一试/证明你是个伪君子
Means either you thought it was a chance/worth taking,making you a hypocrite,
要不就是你指望他搞砸/证明你蛇蝎心肠
or you thought he'd fail,making/you a cutthroat little pixie.
- 是什么导致了.../- Takayasu氏综合症
- What causes- -/takayasu's syndrome.
得伴有皮疹和发热
Not without a rash and a fever.
- 肯定是韦普尔氏病/- 没可能
- It's gotta be whipple's./- No way.
- 韦普尔氏病伴有腹部疼痛/- 别说啦!
- You ever see whipple's without abdominal pain?/- Stop it!
这争吵干扰这儿/每一个男人和女同志的注意力
This argument is distracting/every male and lesbian here.
你们说的都有理/也同时驳斥了对方的观点
You're both right in the sense that/you've convinced me that you're both wrong.
原发性心肌症怎么样?
What about cardiomyopathy?
结构性畸形引发了心脏病发和脑血栓
Structural abnormality causes the heart/attack and throws clots to the brain,
造成共感觉
leading to synesthesia.
- 你几岁了?/- 我21
- How old are you?/- I'm 21.
除非你能说明那跟这有联系
Unless it's relevant.
好吧 小阿飞
Okay,scooter.
去做个经食管心动图
Do a transesophageal echo.
鉴于26可以被2和13整除 他们做你助手
And since the positive divisors of/26 are 2 and 13,have them assist.
剩下的 到自助餐厅去/找出10个能导致炎症的物体源
Rest of you,go to the cafeteria,document/ten things that can cause infection.
每人十个
Each.
最好别吃
I wouldn't.
有个叫17的人说奶酪上可能有李氏杆菌
Someone named "17" thinks there/could be listeria in the cream cheese.
17是个呆瓜数字
17's a stupid number.
- Chase在这儿做什么?/- 你看到Chase?
- What's chase doing here?/- You saw chase?
昨天晚上 在我办公室外边
Last night,outside my office.
有意思
That's interesting.
我比较好奇的是...
It's more curious/than actually--
Chase接受了亚利桑那州Mayo诊所的聘请
chase took a job at the/mayo clinic in arizona.
都一周了
A week ago.
有意思
Interesting.
你 看见 的不是Foreman或Cameron
It wasn't foreman or cameron you "saw,"
而是Chase 被你炒掉的那个
but chase,the one you fired.
没趣了
Not interesting.
相貌相似的人/走过我的办公室而已
Someone who looked like someone I/used to know walked by my office.
被压抑的负罪感开始释放/总是有趣的
It's always interesting when repressed/guilt starts unrepressing itself.
我唯一负罪的是做了这个
The only thing I feel/guilty for is this.
我们将把这内透镜放入你的食道
We're gonna feed this/endoscope down your esophagus,
以便找出心脏哪儿受了损伤
try to find where your/heart might be damaged.
你会觉得不太舒服
It's gonna feel uncomfortable.
坚持一直吞就可以了
But just keep swallowing.
我保证你会没事的
I promise you'll be fine.
她准备好了
She's ready.
上吧 来一击
Go ahead. Take a whack.
如果什么也找不到的话 House怪的是我
Right. So if we don't find/anything,house blames me.
- 你要是找到了 他给你一朵小红花/- 你自己为什么不做?
- Or you find something and get a gold star./- Why don't you want to do it?
白发苍苍的老医生做他第1000次心动图/House会另眼相看么?
House isn't gonna be impressed by a/gray hair doing his ten thousandth echo.
你起疑心了?
That makes you suspicious.
你是?
Doctor?
叫13就可以
Call me "13.
用不着攀交情
" I'm not getting invested.
她的心脏结构完好
Her heart's structurally sound.
没有拴塞或阀门问题
No clots. No valvular defects.
也没有内壁运动失常
No wall motion abnormalities.
你说结构完好的时候我就明白了
Got that from "structurally sound.
- 她说什么?/- 结构完好
- what did she say?/- Structurally sound.
你们这一路跟着我/不会是要说找不出问题的吧
I assume you're not all walking/with me to tell me you found nothing.
有一个短脉冲--
It showed a short/burst in the at--
够的 下一个?
okay.Who's next?
心房扑动有一个短脉冲
Showed a short burst of atrial flutter.
- 我做了两次节奏测试得到一样的结果/- 别说了
- I ran a rhythm strip twice and got the same result./- Stop.
好了 移动式诊断讨论的规矩是
Okay,here's how we diagnose in transit.
我带头 你们跟
I lead,you draft.
我动 你们动
I move,you move.
我停 你们停 明白没?
I stop,you stop. Got it?
- 心房扑动可能是由于荷尔蒙过度分泌/- 怎么是你做的测试?
- Flutter can mean hormone overproduction./- Why did you do the test?
我叫阿飞做的
I gave it to scooter.
- 我们不知道这有什么关系/- 没关系
- We didn't think it/mattered- - it doesn't.
你让她做 这件事有点儿关系
It matters that you let her.
好了
Okay.
10号 24号 39号 去做促甲状腺素释放兴奋试验/看是不是甲状腺机能亢进
10,24,39,run a trh stimulation/test for hyperthyroidism.
那很可能造成另一次心脏病发作
That could cause another heart attack.
就好证明第一次发作由甲状腺导致...
Proving her first attack/was caused by her thyroid.
也算物有所值吧?
Which is kinda the point,right?
我习惯一个人乘
I ride alone.
荷尔蒙会刺激你的甲状腺
The hormones stimulate your thyroid.
如果你开始发热出汗 别担心
Don't worry if you get/flushed or you start to sweat.
说明甲状腺正在起作用
It means the thyroid's working.
如果你愿意的话/我能帮你去掉这个胎记
And,uh,if you want,I/can remove that mole.
我是个整形医生/爱美之心 人皆有之
I'm a plastic surgeon. You're/allowed a little vanity.
我对我的样子很满意
I'm fine with the way I look.
那很好
Good for you.
可让我奇怪的是
Although,I do find it/a bit odd that someone
一个如此自信的人会不想让医生/找出她到底有什么问题
so self-assured doesn't want her doctors/to find out what's wrong with her.
你这话什么意思 那我来这儿干什么?
What are you talking/about? Why else am I here?
你把我们耍得团团转
You're jerking us around.
你的这些限制对我们来说就像手铐一样
You're handcuffing us with/all these restrictions.
我觉得很热
I'm feeling warm.
她的脉搏到120了 别再逼她
Her pulse is 120. Stop pushing.
如果House觉得我们对付不了这/他不会接下这个案子
If house thought this would handicap/us,he wouldn't have taken the case.
或许这就是他接手的原因
Or maybe that's why he took the case.
他想看看我们能不能自己逼出真相
He wants to see if we can/get it out of her on our own.
你们在她家找到什么了?
What did you find in her home?
- 你们去了我家?/- 没什么
- You were in my home?/- Nothing.
旅行照片 校友录 工资单?
Travel pictures,yearbook,her/name on an employment slip?
我们没去看那种东西好不好?
We weren't checking for that stuff,okay?
显然House不希望我们看
Obviously,house didn't want us to.
你们会把我供出去对不对?
You're gonna-- you're/gonna out me,aren't you?
你们会毁掉一切的
You're gonna ruin everything.
没人要做任何事 冷静放松
Nobody's trying to do/anything. Just relax.
这不该是测试的正常反应 脉搏和血压太高了
This is not a normal response to/the test. Pulse and bp are too high.
从我身边走开
Get away from me.
无导联
NO LEADS
走开
Get away from me.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
在我看的时候呼我/可不怎么讨喜欢阿
Paging me during judge judy,not/the best way to win my affections.
她又出现共感觉了
She had another episode of synesthesia.
导致了精神紊乱攻击
It set off a psychotic attack.
现在她跑进那里面 用东西抵住了门把手
And now she ran in there and must've/jammed something in the handles.
这你就呼我 我只有一条好腿/根本无法作用杆杠原理(踹门)
So you call me,the guy with/one good leg and zero leverage.
我们强行打开门的话 保安就会来/她的名字就必然被记录
Uh,we break that door down,security/shows up,and her name goes in a file.
幸运的是 暴力并不是唯一的解决方法
Luckily,violence is not the last resort.
威胁才是 上吧
Extortion is. So go ahead.
威胁她
Extort her.
如果你不把门打开 我们就撞门了
If you don't open this/door,we're going to break it down.
聪明
Clever.
如果她关心医院财产的话 倒是有吸引力
An appeal to her deep/concern for hospital property.
看看效果怎么样
Let's see how that works.
- 如果你不开门 你就会死/- 走开!
- If you don't open this door,you're going to die./- Go away!
有进步
You seem to be getting to her.
她才不在乎是死是活
She doesn't care if she dies.
你觉得她不想活了?
You think she wants to die?
部 我觉得她只想活在特定的条件下
No,but I think she only wants to/live under certain circumstances.
不开门 我就把你的秘密告诉全世界
Open up or I blab your/secret to everyone.
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything.
我知道
I do.
不
No.
有没有镇静剂
Anybody think that/a sedative might--
- 我在试/- 好吧
- I'm trying./- ok
怎么回事?
Who's that?
她是谁?
Who is she?
奥萨马·本·拉登
Osama bin laden.
她是谁?
Who is she?
她还好吧?
Is she okay?
情况稳定了
She's stable.
她是谁?
Who is she?
House怎么告诉你的?
What did house tell you?
说她是从一个跨国犯罪组织逃出来的
That she is on the run from an/international crime syndicate.
他也是这么告诉我们的
That's what he told us.
House也许能算你们的老板/但我是House的老板
House may be your/boss,but I'm house's boss.
你们想在这儿工作 是我说的算
You want to work here,I/better be okay with it.
说实话/他没告诉我们任何关于这个女人的--
Honestly,he didn't tell us/anything about who she was--
她名叫Greta Cooper
her name's greta cooper.
想要成为宇航员
Wants to be an astronaut.
不想让NASA知道她的大脑/正把她的眼睛和耳朵混淆
Doesn't want nasa to know her brain's/getting her ears confused with her eyes.
我查了她的信件
I went through her mail.
你真像个病菌 House
You're a virus,house.
现在不是1个麻烦了 变成20个了
Now instead of one liability,I've got 20.
现在只有19个了
Apparently,only 19.
几号告的密?
Which number was it?
从现在起 你所作所为都得记录
From now on,everything you do gets charted.
白纸黑字
With pen on paper.
文件夹的封面印着普林斯顿教学医院
In a binder that says princeton plainsboro teaching hospital on the cover.
妈妈!
Mom!
如果你要用实验室 我得要份报告
If you want to run something through the labs,I get a copy.
用扫描仪 我也要一份
If you do scans,I get a copy.
你想要用扫描仪 我还要一份
If you think about doing scans,I get a copy.
既然你知道我现在想什么?
You know my current thoughts,right?
就不用写下来了
I don't have to put those on paper.
三件事
Three issues.
第一
One.
10号 你被炒了
#10,you're fired.
她告诉你了?
She told you?
肯定是去过她家的人
Well,it had to be someone who went to her home.
26号 犯困呢
#26 is half asleep.
错过了午睡时间
Missed his afternoon nap.
他倒没有不好意思
Obviously he doesn't feel guilt.
2号怕给签证惹麻烦
#2 is here on a visa she can't jeopardize--
你不该这么肯定
you can't know.
我进来后 那个小妞一直在对你指指点点
And that chick's been pointing at you since I walked in.
第二件事
Issue two.
什么导致了共感 高红细胞/心律不齐和惊恐发作?
What causes synesthesia,high rbc,tachyarrhythmia,and panic attacks?
轻微的葡萄糖升高--
Slight glucose elevation--
暗示了甲状腺问题
that says thyroid.
促甲状腺素基线 1.1
Baseline thyrotropin's 1.1
- 1.3/- 随便啦
- 1.3/- whatever.
反正 她的甲状腺还是好的
Her thyroid's working.
那她的肝脏呢?
What about her liver?
原始的丙氨酸转氨酶水平正常/但也危险了
Original a.L.T.Levels weren't abnormal but were near the edge.
- 她的PDA里面有病人信息/- 我才没有
- She has patient data on her pda./- I do not.
我看到化验数据了
I saw the lab values.
你叫我们别写东西
You said we couldn't write anything down.
我还说过 我要答案
I also said I wanted answers.
肝癌最有可能
Liver cancer's the most likely.
副癌综合症
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
得做核磁共振
We need to do an mri.
这就说到了第三个问题
Which brings us to issue three.
你是说 我们能写东西咯?
You're saying we can write stuff down?
对你 我说你被炒了
To you,I'm saying you're fired.
对其他人呢 我意思是--
To everyone else,I'm saying--
但你特别提到--
but you said specifically--
我讨厌告密者
I hate tattletales.
她揭发了10号
She tattled on 10.
你又告密咯
Now you tattled twice.
第三件事-- 快点 走人吧
Issue three-- come on,let's go.
第三件事
Issue three.
如果不能做测试/怎样才能完成测试呢?
How do we do tests when we can't do tests?
Cuddy医生没说不能做测试
Dr.Cuddy didn't say we can't do tests.
她只说我们得记录到病历
She said we have to chart.
如果要记录 肯定得不到病人同意
If we chart,we won't get consent.
因此不能
So we can't.
病人同不同意可能影响她的性命
The patient's life may depend on her consenting.
她只有不同意 才能继续飞行员的梦想
Her dreams depend on her not consenting.
所以 没法做测试时 怎么做测试呢?
So how do we do tests when we can't do tests?
你们有一个小时去想
You've got an hour.
不用扫描 怎么扫描肝脏呢?
How do you scan a liver without scanning a liver?
还有 Cameron在这干嘛?
And what's cameron doing here?
有意思
Interesting.
现在 你"看见"Cameron了
So you're seeing cameron now.
不 没意思/我不是"看见" 而是"看到了"
No,not "interesting," because not "seeing." "saw."
我病人不会同意做核磁共振和超声波的
my patient won't consent to mris or ultrasounds.
这里 你对付肝癌最有经验
And you've dealt with more liver cancer than anyone else here.
你想我和你分享/我在尼泊尔学到的秘密扫描术?
So you want me to share the secret scanning techniques I learned in nepal?
遗憾地是 那儿的僧人让我发了一个血誓
Unfortunately,the monks made me swear a blood oath.
她当时在哪?
Where was she?
大厅
In the lobby.
我们可以触摸探查肝周围的区域
Guess we could palpate the area around the liver.
除非肿瘤很大 否则是没用的/这点你清楚的
Which won't work unless the tumor's enormous,which you know.
这说明/你来这是因为那些幻觉把你吓坏了
Which means you're here because these visions are freaking you out.
她是一头金发
She had blonde hair.
为什么我会幻想到这个?
Why would I hallucinate that?
是啊
Yes.
是啊 你为什么会把/Cameron和Chase的形象融合起来?
Yes,why are you merging cameron and chase?
我们得找找原因 否则你下次看到她/她就成黑人了
We should find out before the next time you see her when she'll be black.
嗯 科学地讲 一个人回到/工作过的地方是不可能的咯?
Mm-hmm,of course,it's scientifically impossible for a/person to go back and visit somewhere they worked.
也不是
No.
但她既然不是只死猫/(出自物理假设 薛定谔的猫)
But since she's not a dead cat,
科学地讲 她同时现身两处是不可能的
it is scientifically impossible for/her to be in two places at once.
物理笑话
Physics joke.
真是听不够啊
Don't hear enough of those.
她刚从亚利桑那打电话给我
She just called me from arizona.
注意区号
Notice the area code.
"480"
480.
在Scottsdale 他们给了她份工作
They put an offer on a place in scottsdale.
你开口 还是我来?
Do you want to talk or should I?
我们俩都说好了
I guess we could both talk.
他们订婚了
Although they're engaged.
如果你和他们保持联络/你也许要送他们
And if you're staying in touch,you might want to buy them.
也许不是压抑的内疚感发作
Maybe it's not repressed guilt.
可能 你只是恐慌而已
Maybe it's just panic.
现在 你手下人多得都能造铁路了
Right now you've got enough fellows to build a railroad.
但你得把那满屋子的号码/消减到三人
But you're gonna have to narrow that room full of numbers down to three people.
你能把你的机智推断/应用到我病人的肝上吗?
Any chance you could turn this creative brilliance towards my patient's liver?
我觉得你用人 和他们的技术无关
I think you're gonna choose people for reasons that have nothing to do with their skills.
你选中的人 只因为你受不了他们
I think you're going to choose people just because you can't stand them.
因为你一旦喜欢上他们 那就...
Because if you like them,well,that's just.
太有压力了
Stressful.
压力
Stress.
我喜欢
I like it.
得对病人的肝脏施加压力
We need to stress the patient's liver.
你说 让她不适?
You mean make her sick?
我是说 让她身体有特定的故障
I mean make her sick in a specific way.
如果她的肝脏会失灵/那就制造故障看看
If her liver's given to malfunctioning,we make it malfunction.
我们可以这么做吗?
Are we on the other side of wrong here?
难道不应该先咨询下道德准则理事会吗?
Don't we have an ethics board that we should consult?
我不是炒了你嘛
I fired you.
不 你没有
No,you didn't.
他炒了你
He fired you.
你是6号
You're #6.
不 不是 我是9号
No,I'm not.I'm #9.
你恬不知耻 我很欣赏
I approve of your shamelessness.
但你还是被炒了
You're still fired.
怎样给她的肝脏施压?
How do we stress her liver?
撒谎和糊弄报告 我能接受/但停掉她的器官运--
Lying and paperwork,I get.Shutting down organs--
可以给她静脉注射维生素D/然后把她绑在沙滩椅上晒太阳
we could give her intravenous vitamin d and stick her in a tanning booth.
如果她昏迷了/就知道是新陈代谢的问题
If she goes into a coma,we know it's a metabolic problem.
不错
Nice.
但是维生素D通过肝脏和肾来代谢
But vitamin d's metabolized by the liver and kidneys.
不能告诉我们 哪个器官坏了
It wouldn't tell us which one's screwed up.
可以把她灌醉
We could get her wasted.
给她喝龙舌兰酒 看她多久才醉晕
Give her shots of tequila.Measure how long it takes for her to pass out.
如果太快/就知道她的肝脏没在代谢酒精
If it's too fast,then we know her liver's not processing alcohol.
值得一试
It's a shot.
我喜欢你 9号
I like you,#9.
你找我?
You wanted to see me?
你是摩门教徒?
You a mormon?
你带着杨百翰大学的戒指/(全美最大的摩门教教会学校)
You're wearing a ring from brigham young.
还是说 你们家只是整理草坪的校工?
Or did your folks just do the lawns?
教会对种族平等问题的态度在进步
The church has a very progressive attitude toward racial equality.
我才不关心呢
Don't care.
其实 我心系上帝
Actually,I'm thanking god.
你是我们中唯一一个不喝酒的
You're the only non-drinker we got.
我们得弄一个参照组 看看肝脏的/衰退程度是否在合理范围之内
We need a control group to establish whether the liver's deterioration is within normal range.
找到一个老酒鬼 一个适度酒鬼
Got a big drinker,medium drinker,
现在找到一个滴酒不沾的
now I got a no-drinker.
做核磁共振吧
Just do an mri.
你真的认为 那个创造了天堂
You really think the guy who created heaven
和人间的家伙 真的在乎你喝什么吗?/(摩门教不允许喝酒)
and earth cares what you put in your digestive tract?
她的梦想不应该凌驾于我的信仰之上
Her dream shouldn't outrank my religious belief.
为什么不?
Why not?
她的梦想可能成真啊
Her dream might come true.
生命是神圣的 不是吗?
All life is sacred,right?
我们不是在救她的命/只不过是诊断测试
We're not saving her life,we're doing a diagnostic test.
甚至不是真正的诊断测试
Not even a real diagnostic test.
这个假测试可能真的会救她一命
Well,that fake test might really save her life.
你们中间谁有驴或牛在安息日掉在井里/不立时拉它上来呢?
Would you pull an ass out of a pit on the sabbath?
你在安息日那天 会不会给人治病?/(引自路加福音14:5 耶稣应对质疑)
Would you or would you not pull an ass out of a pit on the sabbath?
好吧
Fine.
我做
I'll do it.
很好
Good.
为啥你们非要选龙舌兰酒?
Why'd you have to pick tequila?
单一麦芽酒的效果也差不多嘛
I assume a single malt would've worked just as well.
不是我们选的
Wasn't our choice.
好
Okay.
两分钟 然后进行第五轮
Two minutes,then round number five.
跟我说说那个摩门神奇内衣吧
So tell me about the magic underwear.
为了这你留在这里?
Is that why you're here?
我就是那个老酒鬼
I'm the big drinker.
完成我那部分测试
Doing my part for science.
有意思的是 比起她的梦想/为什么你的宗教信仰不那么重要了?
The interesting question is why your religious beliefs are suddenly less important than her dreams.
你在驳回你的观点吗?
You're reversing your argument?
我知道自己信仰什么
I know what I believe.
我只是不清楚你信仰什么
I'm just not quite sure what you believe.
后期圣徒教会(即摩门教)并不是/要指挥生活中所有的细枝末节
Well,lds doesn't try to dictate every detail of our lives.
情形迷茫不清的时候/我们被鼓励自己做决定
When a situation isn't clear,we're encouraged to make our own decisions.
但你的判断 是拒绝呀
But your judgment was to say no.
你采纳了我的论断
You used my judgment.
你的论断能服人
You made a good argument.
合理的论断对信奉宗教之人没用
Rational arguments don't usually work on religious people.
否则就没有信仰宗教的人了
Otherwise there would be no religious people.
你是个无神论者
You're an atheist.
只在圣诞节和复活节时
Only on christmas and easter.
其他时候 这重要吗?
The rest of the time,it doesn't really matter?
这样 又有什么乐趣可言?
Where's the fun in that?
一个有限的 毫不神秘的世界--
A finite,unmysterious universe--
这和乐趣无关
it's not about fun.
而和事实有关
It's about the truth.
事实是 我们吵起来了/是因为你想研究我这人
The truth is,we're having this debate because you want to figure something out about me.
目前为止 你有什么结论?
What do you got so far?
Greta Greta
Greta.Greta.
她喘不过气了 我们得插管
She can't breathe.We need to intubate.
起码得供氧
At least oxygen.
NASA会刨根问底的
Nasa will need to know why.
我查看了你要求进行的测试
I checked the tests you ordered.
你刚刚看见了Foreman了吗?
Did you just see foreman?
你测量了她的牙齿密度
You measured the density of her teeth.
这是检测高钙血症的捷径
It's a shortcut test for hypercalcemia.
你刚才肯定和他擦身而过了
You had to have just passed him.
你在病患毫无骨折迹象的情况下/怀疑她得了高钙血症?
So you suspected hypercalcemia from her complete lack of broken bones.
你还为此做了三次毒理检查吗?
Is that why you also ran three tox screens.
病患可能偷吃兴奋剂
Patient might've been sneaking uppers.
他穿着白大褂 你重新雇用他了?
He was in a white coat.Did you hire him back?
Foreman现在纽约Mercy医院/负责诊断科
Foreman is running the diagnostic department at new york mercy.
你喝酒了?
Have you been drinking?
病患呼吸困难
She was having trouble breathing.
拒绝输氧和插管
Refused oxygen and intubation.
所以你们就把她弄到跑步机上?
So you put her on a treadmill.
这样报告上就会注明/是在常规心脏负荷测试中给她吸氧
Records will show that we gave her oxygen as a part of a routine cardio stress test.
病患呼吸得以恢复正常
She gets to breathe.
给上司的报告也无懈可击
Your boss gets her paperwork.
这是谁的主意?
Who's idea was that?
这是通力合作的成果
It was a joint decision.
才怪
It never is.
你哥哥离家出走时，你多大了?
So how old were you when your brother left home?
- 你凭什么认为…/- 你为什么不回答?
- Why do you think-/- why aren't you answering?
离婚是你妈妈提出来的?
Did your mother initiate the divorce?
该关注的是她的肺部到底出了什么问题
We should probably focus on what's wrong with her lungs.
你是女巫吗?
Are you a wiccan?
她的确无法呼吸
She really can't breathe.
好 稳住别动
Okay,hold still.
你在干嘛?
What are you doin'?
听叩诊
Auscultatory percussion.
耳灵则行
If you have a good ear,you can.
你朋友不多 因为你--
You didn't have a lot of friends because you--
你能边听边说?
you can hear while you're talking?
不光能测到构造细节/还能摸到皮下小结块
You can detect not only structural details,but small,deep masses.
游戏到此为止
Game's over.
你不是得了肺癌 就是结节性硬化症
You either have lung cancer or tuberous sclerosis.
我们得对你做活检手术
We need to cut you open and biopsy.
那会…
That'll.
留下疤痕的
Leave a scar.
宇航局的医生看到了 就完了
Nasa doctors will see.They'll know.
我没给斯普林斯汀(歌手)开过刀/没和巴巴拉·费尔顿(演员)上过床
I never opened for springsteen or slept with barbara feldon.
没有梦想 你也能活好多年
You can live for years without dreams.
可没了肺…
Without lungs.
你想办法
Find a way.
好吧
Okay.
只要你说话够硬气,你就死不了
As long you keep saying it strongly,you won't die.
想—
Find.
个办法出来
A way.
如何迫使病人进行手术?
How do we force a patient into surgery?
德州皮包骗局?
Texas bag scam?
萨拉托加电缆?/(美国纽约州东部村落 温泉疗养地)
Saratoga wire?
游览巴黎展览会?
Paris exposition trip?
手术不是问题
The problem's not the surgery.
问题出在疤痕上
It's the scars.
有整形医师可以除去疤痕
And we have a plastic surgeon here who can hide 'em.
没那么神
Not that well.
宇航局会进行彻底的全身检查
Nasa's gonna check every cranny.
我说干脆在她的氧气里加点乙醚/然后该干嘛干嘛
I say we just put ether in her oxygen and do what we have to do.
她会起诉的
She'll sue.
起诉什么?
For what?
起诉我们让她无法欺骗政府吗?
Making it harder for her to lie to the government?
呃 倒不必隐藏疤痕
Uh,we don't need to hide them.
对她进行选择性整容外科手术
We give her elective cosmetic surgery.
通过切口 可以对其肺部进行手术/而她也可为疤痕提供合理的解释
The incisions will give us access to her lungs and she's got an innocent explanation for the scars.
你是指 吸脂术?
You mean like liposuction.
不
No,no.
那样的切口离肺部太远
Uh,those incisions are too far from the lungs.
我们不抽除物质 而是添加
We don't subtract,we add.
把她由B杯升级到C杯
Turn her "b"s into "c"s.
传说假波在高海拔处会破裂
It's a myth that fake hooters blow up at high altitude.
她会没事的
She'll be fine.
就把这当作人类的一大飞越吧
Just think of it as one giant rack for mankind.
我奋斗了这么多年就是为了让人另眼相看
I fought for years to be taken seriously.
相信我 你一定会让人刮目相看的
Trust me,you'll be taken more seriously.
签了这表格
Just sign the form.
这会让我颜面尽失
This'll make me a joke.
肯定还有其他办法
There's got to be another way.
我 认识不少心怀大志的人
I've,uh,known a few people who had dreams.
他们的共同之处在于/就算被人嘲笑也会不以为意
One thing they all had in common was they got laughed at and they didn't care.
你为了隆胸手术取消了一个脾切除手术?
You bumped a splenectomy for a boob job?
和她说话时 人人只看她的脸不看她的胸/你忍心让这女人一辈子都这么痛苦吗?
Would you condemn this woman to a life where people look at her face when they talk to her?
你不解释清楚 我就取消手术
You don't explain this,I'll cancel the surgery.
我能解析下为什么你来这吗?
Can I explain why you're here?
我刚刚说过了为什么我--
Think I just told you why I--
我要给诊断病患做隆胸手术/这实在是匪夷所思
I scheduled a diagnostic patient for a boob job,which is ridiculous.
因此很显然你得来质问我
So obviously you had to confront me.
到目前为止 说的没错
With you so far.
不过我会给你个理由
But I'm gonna give you a reason.
理由不充分
Not a good one.
是不充分
No.
连充分的边都沾不上
Not even close to a good one.
但这理由会动摇你的观点
But here's the drag from your point of view.
因为我的解释是会有道理的
My explanation will make sense.
董事会不理解
Not to the board.
法官不会理解
Not to a judge.
但你会
But to you.
所以你会支持我
So you'll let me do it.
然后在行政听证会上 你会坐在我身边
Then you're gonna have to sit next to me at the administrative hearing.
你没有更要紧的事要做吗?
Don't you have better things to do?
完全是为了病患的利益
It's in the best interests of the patient.
套针进入体内
Trocar's in.
你可以开始了
You're good to go.
清除肺部气体
Deflate the lung.
那儿
There.
有个囊肿
A cyst.
不止一个
Cysts.
我看到了三个
I count three of them.
左边肺部至少也有这么多
Probably the same if not more on the left lung.
究竟是什么在夜以继日地/谋害"本·拉登小姐"?
Okay,so what's been working overtime to kill "miss bin laden"?
我们现在知道她名字了
We know her name now.
是 可我又忘了
Yeah,but I forgot it.
念出神奇的咒语 免除下一次的考验
Say the magic word and get immunity from the next challenge.
泡球蚴病
Alveolar hydatid disease.
侵袭所有器官
Hits all the organs.
那她现在应该已经出现多次痉挛才是
She would've have multiple seizures by now.
肺朗格罕氏细胞组织细胞增多症
Pulmonary langerhans'.
无法解释红血细胞增多
Doesn't explain the red blood cells.
使劲想
Come on.
囊肿 共感觉 心脏病
Cysts.Synesthesia.Heart attack.
- 你们应该-/- 林岛综合症
- You guys have gotten-/- von hippel-lindau syndrome.
导致红细胞数量增加
Raises red blood cell count.
在器官内生成结块
Causes masses on the organs.
结块中的一种是肾上腺髓质瘤
One of the masses is a pheochromocytoma.
它会诱发神经性疾病和心脏病
It'd cause neurologic episodes and a heart attack.
你看到上面站了个乳臭未干的金发小子吗?
Do you see a blond guy who still has peach fuzz standing up there?
本次手术属封闭式
This is a closed procedure.
不对外开放演示
Gallery's off limits.
外科部医生例外
Not to the surgical staff.
你打算雇用他 不要我们吗?
You gonna hire that guy instead of us?
门都没有
Not a chance.
我爱死你们了
I love you guys.
切除囊肿/进行显微解剖以确诊林岛综合症
Dig out the cysts,histology to confirm von hippel-lindau.
别忘了给她隆胸
Don't forget her chesticles.
亚利桑那州的来电
Calling arizona.
妙招啊
It was a very nice touch.
- 你确实对他们余情未了/- 不但没有余情未了
- You do have residual-/- not only do I not have residual feelings,
我对他们一丁点感情都没有
I didn't even have primary feelings.
- 你吓坏-/- 你撒谎了
- You freaked-/- you lied.
- 因为你明白这表示-/- 没有任何含义！
- Because you knew it meant-/- it meant nothing!
我看到他是因为他就在那
I saw him 'cause he was there.
Cameron跟着她的小亲亲一起去了外科部?
Did cameron follow herbeshert to the surgery department?
我觉得是Chase跟着她来了
I think chase followed her.
她是急诊部的主治医师 三周前来的
She's been a senior attending in the E.R.The last three weeks.
金发主治医师,这么说更精确
A blonde senior attending,to be accurate.
Foreman
Foreman.
他回神经科了?
Is he back in neurology?
他在纽约的Mercy医院
He's at new york mercy.
他在那工作一个月了
He's been there a month.
你也"看见"Foreman了?
Did you "see" foreman?
没有
No.
那么我已经好了
So I'm cured.
目前来说是的
You're fine for now.
不过林岛综合症是一种遗传性疾病
But von hippel-lindau is a genetic disease.
无法彻底治愈
There's no cure.
Greta 你应该向NASA坦白
Greta,you need to come clean to nasa.
所有的囊肿不是都摘除了吗?
You said you got all the cysts.
可能再生
They could reemerge.
我会去放射科
I'll go to radiology clinics.
我会定期拍片检查
I'll get regular screenings.
如果你在天上的时候 出了什么差错
If something happened while you're up there,
你这就像是在赌俄罗斯轮盘--
you'd be playing russian roulette with--
别紧张
relax.
她不用去坦白 你也不用
She doesn't have to neither do you.
结果NASA的医生对林岛综合症/毫不陌生
Turns out that nasa doctors even know where the hyphen in von hippel-lindau goes.
你通知他们了?
You called them?
我又不是白痴
I'm not an idiot.
航天飞机会经过新泽西州的
Those shuttles fly over new jersey.
现在我们到了
So here we are.
揭晓答案的最后时刻
The big moment.
谁会留下来继续忍受折磨?
Which of you gets to live to be abused another day.
谁会回家反省/找出被炒鱿鱼的原因以重塑性格?
And which of you goes home and rationalizes being fired as character building?
持如下号码的各位 感谢你们的参与
Following numbers,thanks for playing.
21  19  8  34  17  29  5  36  2
21,19,8,34,17,29,5,36,2.
剩下的各位 明早八点不许迟到
Rest of you,8:00 a.M.Sharp.
我大概在十点到三点之间来
I'll be in sometime between 10:00 and 3:00.
不过26号,稍等一下
But 26,stick around awhile.
我没出任何差错
I did nothing wrong.
很多人都没出差错
Lots of people did nothing wrong.
其他人搞砸了 我可从没--
Other people screwed up.I never even--
其他人把握住了机会
other people took chances.
26号
26.
- 过敏 但-/- 是的 我知道
- Lergic to-/- yeah,I know.
你贵庚?
How old are you?
21岁
21.
你觉得年龄无关紧要
You don't think it's relevant.
你传授的医术/可能我实践的时间会短一点
I'll likely have less time to use the skills you teach us,
不过我觉得这对你来说无关紧要
but I don't think that's significant to you.
那你从没念过医学院这事怎么说?
How about the fact that you never went to medical school,
这也是你让别人做经食道心动图的原因吧?
which is why you let the unlucky number do the trans echo?
幸好你虽缺乏职业道德/但还有一点道德原则
At least you're ethically unethical.
我在哥伦比亚大学医学院的招生办/干了三十年
30 years I worked in the columbia med school admissions office.
旁听了所有的课程
Audited all the classes.
大部分还听了不止一次
Most of them more than once.
可就是拿不到文凭
I just never got a diploma.
你知道我迟早会发现的吧
You had to know I'd find out sooner or later.
我知道你不墨守成规
I know you break rules.
我本以为也许你会为我破例一次
I thought maybe you'd break one for me.
我不能雇你当医生
I can't hire you as a doctor,
但你可以继续告诉我 你的想法
but you can still tell me what you think.
你也可以帮我递咖啡 拿干洗的衣服
You can also fetch me coffee,pick up my dry-cleaning,
直到我决定到底留不留你
until I can decide whether or not to keep you.
那么我参与这场海选的身份是
So I'm playing this whole game to be like.
你的秘书?
Your secretary?
秘书听着有辱身份 助理听着就好多了
Assistant sounds marginally less demeaning.
这可不是我梦寐以求的工作
It's not my dream job.
实际上是的
Actually,it is.
只不过不是你梦寐以求的头衔罢了
It's just not your dream title.
三周了
Three weeks.
你不是从来观察得细致入微吗/这次可遗漏很多了
For someone who never misses something small,you missed something big.
你是个白痴
You're an idiot.
头发还是我的工作/还是两者皆是?
The hair,where I'm working,or both?
这头发让你看起来像妓女
The hair makes you look like a hooker.
我喜欢
I like it.
在出车祸的倒霉蛋身上拔挡风玻璃片片
Pulling pieces of windshield out of car accident victims.
把切百吉饼时切断的手指头再接回去
Reattaching fingertips sliced off cutting bagels.
好歹Chase的选择才降了一级
At least chase's move is only one step down.
我在这做的挺好
I can do good here.
换一个环境
Get it out of my system.
你为什么向NASA告发了自己的病患?
Why'd you rat your patient out to nasa?
不知道是谁不谈绯闻性事/爱谈道德原则
I don't know who's been gossiping about ethics instead of sex,
我希望她已经给开除了
but I hope they've already been fired.
几号?
Which number was it?
Greta
Greta.
- 号码/- 没有号码
- Number./- No number.
病患
The patient.
你以为她怎么弄到你的传呼号码的?
How do you think she got your pager number?
她来看急诊
She came into the e.R.
不愿多说
didn't want to talk.
我没告发她
I didn't rat her out.
你撒谎了?
You lied?
看来我该赶在她划花我的车之前/把真相告诉她
Suppose I should tell her that before she keys my car.
为什么撒谎?
Why lie?
免得其他大嘴巴泄露消息
Had to stop some leaking faucets.
泄露了又如何?
What did it matter?
这事和其他人没关系
It was no one's business.
那是
Right.
她会是上面最安全的宇航员
She's gonna be the safest astronaut up there.
她的同事没有察觉到脑瘤随时会爆炸  /而她警觉得多
Certainly more vigilant than the guy next to her/who's got no clue about the aneurysm in his head ready to pop.
是的
Right.
你有更好的理由?
You got a better reason?
你无法夺走她的梦想
You couldn't kill her dream.
-=豪斯医生=-/第四季 第2集 /"征空先锋"; "the Right Stuff"
- 未翻译字幕 -